{
    "subject": "resource/Frank_Miller_(Medal_of_Honor)",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York_City",
    "human_readable": "Frank Miller was born in New York City.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9168640375137329,
            "question": "Where was Frank Miller born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36729055643081665,
            "question": "Name some popular works by Frank Miller."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28409892320632935,
            "question": "Where did Frank Miller's artistic inspiration come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21995195746421814,
            "question": "What is Frank Miller famous for creating?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16128595173358917,
            "question": "Is Frank Miller known for his work in comics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12517507374286652,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Frank Miller's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1139829158782959,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Frank Miller's stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09313473850488663,
            "question": "What other creative fields has Frank Miller worked in besides comics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09034053236246109,
            "question": "Did Frank Miller influence the graphic novel genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0896034687757492,
            "question": "How has Frank Miller's style influenced later comic book artists?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frank Miller was born in New York City.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2809_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Frank Miller influence the graphic novel genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2809_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other creative fields has Frank Miller worked in besides comics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2809_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in Frank Miller's stories?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2809_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2809_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided describe a person named Frank Miller, but they do not specify that he was born in New York City. In fact, one document mentions that he was born in Olney, Maryland."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not mention that Frank Miller was born in New York City. Instead, they indicate that he was born in Olney, Maryland."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}